Guide to the Montana State University Extension Service Records 1912-1970
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- County and Home Demonstration Agents Annual Reports, 1916-1970; 1
  - Lewis and Clark County; Patricia S. Sias, James F. Sargent, Alma Ragar, Frank Carter, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Lewis and Clark County; James Sargent, Frank Carter, Pat Sias, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Jim Sargent, Frank Carter, Patricia Sias, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Lewis and Clark County, 1967-1970 (Box 35, Folder 26-29)
  - Emergency Report, Liberty and Toole Counties; J. E. Hodgskiss, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Report, Liberty County; Charles Jarrett, Assistant Agent, 1935 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Liberty County; James Sargent, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Liberty County; James F. Sargent, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
  - Liberty County; James F. Sargent, W. Doyle Stocks, John Calhoun, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Liberty County; John H. Calhoun, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Liberty County; John Calhoun, Douglas G. Smith, C.A.s, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Liberty County; Douglas, G. Smith, C.A., 1959 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Liberty County; Douglas G. Smith, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Liberty County; Douglas G. Smith, Anton S. Sundsted, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Liberty County; Anton S. Sundsted, Lee R. Rovig, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Liberty County; Lee Rovig, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Liberty County; Lee R. Rovig, Roger Wilson, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Liberty County; Roger L. Wilson, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Liberty County; Roger Wilson, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Liberty County, 1967-1970 (Box 36, Folder 17-20)
  - Lincoln County; Carl W. Morgan, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Lincoln County; F. A. Givan, 1924-1925 (Box 36, Folder 22-23)
  - Lincoln County; F. A. Givan, C.A., 1926 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Lincoln County; L. T. Winslow, C.A., 1927-1929 (Box 36, Folder 25-27)
  - Lincoln County; W. Mauritson, Emergency Agent, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - SCS Report, Lincoln County; Walt, Mauritson, Assistant Emergency Agent, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Lincoln County; J. Glenn Jones, Assoc. Agent, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Lincoln County; B. F. Robinson, 1947-1950 (Box 36, Folder 31-34)
  - Summary Report, Lincoln County; December 1, 1950-March 15, 1951, B. F. Robinson (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Lincoln County; T. Z. Wojciechowski, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Lincoln County; Thaddeus Wojciechowski, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Lincoln County; T. Z. Wojciechowski, 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 38-39)
  - Lincoln County; Thaddeus Z. Wojciechowski, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Lincoln County; T. Z. Wojciechowski, Orville McCarver, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Lincoln County; T. Z. Wojciechowski, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Lincoln County; Thaddeus Wojciechowski, C.A.; William Richter, C.A. at Large, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Lincoln County; Thad Wojciechowski, Bill Richter, Edward Bratton, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Lincoln County; G. Edward Bratton, 1960-1962 (Box 36, Folder 45-47)
  - Lincoln County; Louis E. Rollman, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Lincoln County; Louis Rollman, 1964-1966 (Box 37, Folder 2-4)
  - Lincoln County, 1967-1970 (Box 37, Folder 5-8)
  - Madison County; H. N. Kauffman, 1921-1923 (Box 37, Folder 9-11)
  - Madison County; H. N. Kauffman, H. C. Burgess, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Madison County; H. C. Burgess, C.A., 1925-1930 (Box 37, Folder 13-18)
  - McCone County; Alberta Coleman, H.D.A., 1930-1931 (Box 37, Folder 19-20)
  - McCone County; Frances Bellamy, H.D.A., 1932 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - McCone County; Frances Baker, Gwendolyn Watts, H.D.A.s, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Emergency Report, McCone County; M. H. Ostrem, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - McCone County; Gwendolyn Watts, H.D.A., 1934 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - McCone County; Thomas Hunt, Emergency Agent, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - McCone County; Gwendolyn A. Watts, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - McCone County; Mrs. Gwendolyn Watts Madson, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - McCone County; Mrs. Gwendolyn Madson, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - McCone County; Mrs. Gwendolyn W. Madson, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - McCone County; Gwendolyn W. Madson, H.D.A., 1939 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - McCone County; Robert A. Roush, C.A., 1947 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - McCone County; Robert A. Roush, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - McCone County; Robert A. Roush, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - McCone County; Leland P. Cade, 1950-1951 (Box 37, Folder 34-35)
  - McCone County; Stanley Parris, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 36-37)
  - McCone County; Homer L. Carter, 1954-1956 (Box 37, Folder 38-40)
  - McCone County; Phillips E. Olmstead, C.A., 1957-1960 (Box 37, Folder 41-44)
  - McCone County; Phillips E. Olmstead, 1961-1964 (Box 38, Folder 1-4)
  - McCone County; Phillips Olmstead, M. Eddie Miller, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - McCone County; Eddie Miller, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - McCone County, 1967-1970 (Box 38, Folder 7-10)
  - Meagher County; H. D. Hunt, Emergency Agent, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Meagher County; E. P. Orcutt, 1937-1939 (Box 38, Folder 12-14)
  - Meagher County; E. P. Orcutt, Carl O. Hansen, C.A.s, 1940 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Meagher County; Carl O. Hansen, C.A., 1941-1944 (Box 38, Folder 16-19)
  - Meagher County; Paul Wylie, W. G. Stucky, C.A.s, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Meagher County; W. G. Stucky, C.A.s, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Meagher County; Matt W. Heaphy, C.A., 1947 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Meagher County; Matt Heaphy, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Meagher County; M. W. Heaphy, 1949-1950 (Box 38, Folder 24-25)
  - Meagher County; James E. Roan, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Meagher County; Wm. Y. Fowler, 1952-1953 (Box 38, Folder 27-28)
  - Meagher County; William Y. Fowler, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Meagher County; T. J. Svaren, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Meagher County; T. J. Svaren, Herbert H. Townsend, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Meagher County; Herbert H. Townsend, C.A., 1957-1960 (Box 38, Folder 32-35)
  - Mineral County; William G. Hiett, Assoc. Agent, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Mineral County; J. E. Wilson, C.A., 1947 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Mineral County; James E. Wilson, 1948-1949 (Box 38, Folder 38-39)
  - Mineral County; Ralph Aaker, 1949-1950 (Box 38, Folder 40-41)
  - Summary of Accomplishments, Mineral County; December 1, 1950-February 28, 1951, Ralph Aaker (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Mineral County; Thomas C. Hiestand, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Mineral County; T. C. Hiestand, Jr., 1952 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Mineral County; Thomas Hiestand, 1953-1954 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
  - Mineral County; Thomas C. Hiestand, Jr., D. Dee Hortin, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Mineral County; D. Dee Horton, C.A., 1956-1959 (Box 39, Folder 4-7)
  - Mineral County; Dee Horton, Robert Ruthemeyer, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Mineral County; Robert Ruthemyer, Noble Dean, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Mineral County; Noble E. Dean, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Mineral County; Noble Dean, John Wicks, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Mineral County; John E. Wicks, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 12-13)
  - Mineral County; Robert Johnson, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Mineral County, 1967-1970 (Box 39, Folder 15-18)
  - Missoula County; Charles L. Hansen, 1914 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Missoula County; Charles Hansen, 1915 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Missoula County; J. R. Campbell, 1916-1918 (Box 39, Folder 21-23)
  - Missoula County; W. E. Pollinger, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Missoula County; H.D.A., 1918-1919 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Missoula County; W. E. Pollinger, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Missoula County; H.D.A., 1920 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Missoula County; M. M. Oliphant, C.A., 1927-1936 (Box 39, Folder 28-37)
  - Missoula County; Helen N. Allen, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Missoula County; M. M. Oliphant, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Missoula County; Miss Helen N. Allen, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Missoula County; M. M. Oliphant, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Missoula County; Helen N. Allen, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Missoula County; M. M. Oliphant, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Missoula County; Helen Allen, H.D.A., 1939 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Missoula County; M. M. Oliphant, C.A., 1940 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Missoula County; Helen Allen, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Missoula County; M. M. Oliphant, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Missoula County; Helen Allen, H.D.A., 1941 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Missoula County; M. M. Oliphant, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Missoula County; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Missoula County; M. M. Oliphant, C.A., 1943 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Missoula County; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Missoula County; M. M. Oliphant, A. R. Rollin, C.A.s, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Missoula County; Lillian Stone, Helen L. Kenworthy, H.D.A.s, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, C.A., 1945 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Missoula County; Helen Kenworthy, Marjorie Jennings, H.D.A.s, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, C.A., 1946 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Missoula County; Marjorie Jennings, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, C.A., 1947 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Missoula County; LaVerne Olsen, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Missoula County; Marjorie I. Jennings, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Missoula County; Mrs. Marjorie I. Jennings, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Missoula County; Mrs. Marjorie Jennings, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Marjorie Jennings, 1951-1952 (Box 40, Folder 21-22)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Anna Pederson, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Richard Pulis, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Richard Pulis, Anna Pederson, Helen G. Emblen, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Helen Emblen, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Helen Emblen, Frank A. Carter, Jeannette Hiett, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Agent; Frank Carter, Agent at Large; Jeannette Hiett, H.D.A., 1958 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, C.A.; Jeannette Hiett, H.D.A., 1959 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Jeannette T. Hiett, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Jeannette T. Hiett, Patricia R. Paugh, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Missoula County; A. R. Rollin, Jeannette Hiett, 1962-1963 (Box 40, Folder 32-33)
  - Missoula County; Thaddeus Wojciechowski, Martha Bingham, Jeannette Hiett, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Missoula County; Thaddeus Wojciechowski, Jean Hiett, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 35-36)
  - Missoula County, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Missoula County, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Missoula County, 1968 December 1-1969 June 30 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Missoula County, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Musselshell County; R. S. Scott, 1917 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Musselshell County, 1918 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Musselshell County; R. S. Scott, 1919 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Musselshell County; J. M. Spain, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Musselshell County; F. B. Peterson, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Musselshell County; F. B. Peterson, C.A., 1931-1933 (Box 41, Folder 8-10)
  - Park County, 1917 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Park County; R. W. Jorgenson, C.A., 1929 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Park County; R. W. Jorgenson, C.A., 1930 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Park County; F. A. Finch, C.A., 1931-1932 (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
  - Park County; H. D. Hurd, C.A., 1934-1936 (Box 41, Folder 16-18)
  - Park County; H. D. Hurd, George L. Hart, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Park County; G. L. Hart, 1938 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Park County; G. l. Hart, 1939 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Park County; Geo. L. Hart, C.A., 1940 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Park County; George L. Hart, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Park County; G. L. Hart, 1942 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Park County; Geo. L. Hart, C.A., 1943 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Park County; Owen S. Wirak, C.A., 1944-1947 (Box 41, Folder 26-29)
  - Park County; Lenix Badger, 1948-1955 (Box 41, Folder 30-37)
  - Park County; Lenix Badger, William J. Cutler, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Park County; Lenix Badger, Thomas N. Glennie, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Park County; Lenix Badger, C.A., 1958 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Park County; Lenix Badger, C.A., 1959 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Park County; Lenix Badger, Tom Glennie, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Park County; Thomas N. Glennie, Lenix Badger, 1961-1966 (Box 42, Folder 3-8)
  - Park County, 1967-1970 (Box 42, Folder 9-12)
  - Petroleum County; P. D. McElliott, Emergency Agent, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Phillips County; Robert Clarkson, 1917 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Phillips County; W. P. Stapleton, 1918-1922 (Box 42, Folder 15-19)
  - Phillips County; W. P. Stapleton, H. L. Lantz, 1923 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Phillips County; H. L. Lantz, 1924-1932 (Box 42, Folder 21-29)
  - Phillips County; H. L. Lantz, C.A., 1933 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Phillips County; H. L. Lantz, H. M, Oefstos, 1934 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Phillips County; Henry M. Oefstos, 1935-1941 (Box 43, Folder 3-9)
  - Phillips County; H. M. Oefstos, W. R. Rasmussen, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Phillips County; W. M. Rasmussen, C.A., 1943-1946 (Box 43, Folder 11-14)
  - Phillips County; H. M. Oefstos, 1947-1954 (Box 43, Folder 15-22)
  - Phillips County; H. M. Oefstos, Elvin A. Powell, Richard Pulis, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Phillips County; H. M. Oefstos, Richard Pulis, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Phillips County; Richard H. Pulis, Thomas N. Glennie, Robert A. Weber, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Phillips County; Richard H. Pulis, C.A., 1958 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Phillips County; Richard Pulis, C.A.; Larry Thayer, C.A.; Donna Qualey, H.D.A., 1959 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Phillips County; Laurence Thayer, Donna Qualey, Stan Bradley, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Phillips County; Donna Qualey, Stanford L. Bradley, Laurence E. Thayer, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Phillips County; Stanford L. Bradley, Donna M. Qualey, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Phillips County; Stanford L. Bradley, Donna Qualey, Jean Stephens, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Phillips County; Stanford Bradley, Roger Brownson, Jean Stephens, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Phillips County; Roger Brownson, Jean Stephens, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Phillips County; Roger Brownson, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Phillips County, 1967-1970 (Box 43, Folder 35-38)
  - Pondera County; Blaine Ferguson, 1923-1924 (Box 43, Folder 39-40)
  - Pondera County; Blaine Ferguson, C.A., 1925-1926 (Box 43, Folder 41-42)
  - Pondera County; Blaine Ferguson, A. C. Petersen, C.A.s, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Pondera County; A. C. Petersen, C.A., 1928-1944 (Box 44, Folder 1-17)
  - Pondera, County; Dorothy Hoylman, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Pondera, County; A. C. Petersen, C.A., 1945 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Pondera, County; Dorothy Hoylman, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Pondera, County; A. C. Petersen, C.A., 1946 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Pondera, County; Conrad- Dorothy Hoylman, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Pondera, County; A. C. Petersen, C.A., 1947 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Pondera, County; Dorothy Elespuru, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Pondera, County; David P. Rice, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Pondera, County; Dorothy Elespuru, Louise Shunk, H.D.A.s, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Pondera, County; David P. Rice, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Pondera, County; Louise S. Shunk, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Pondera, County; L. E. Flesch, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Pondera, County; Louise S. Shunk, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Pondera, County; Charles E. Voss, Louise S. Shunk, 1951-1953 (Box 45, Folder 1-3)
  - Pondera, County; Guy L. Robbins, Louise S. Shunk, 1954-1955 (Box 45, Folder 4-5)
  - Pondera, County; Guy L. Robbins, Louise S. Shunk, Dorothy Gallup, Ramon T. Nile, M. J. Jackson, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Pondera, County; M. J. Jackson, Dorothy E. Gallup, Douglas G. Smith, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Pondera, County; M. J. Jackson, Agent; Douglas Smith, Agent at Large; Mrs. Dorothy Gallup, H.D.A., 1958 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Pondera, County; M. J. Jackson, C.A.; Dorothy Gallup, H.D.A., 1959 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Pondera, County; M. J. Jackson, Stanford L. Bradley, Dorothy E. Gallup, Ardis J. Jarrett, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Pondera, County; M. J. Jackson, Dorothy Gallup, Hugh Maxwell, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Pondera, County; M. J. Jackson, Hugh Maxwell, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Pondera, County; M. J. Jackson, Donna M. Qualey, 1963-1964 (Box 45, Folder 13-14)
  - Pondera, County; Olaf Sherwood, Donna Qualey, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 15-16)
  - Pondera County, 1967-1970 (Box 45, Folder 17-20)
  - Powder River County; Dale D. Bergland, C.A., 1957-1960 (Box 45, Folder 21-24)
  - Powder River County; John W. Jeakins, 1961-1964 (Box 45, Folder 25-28)
  - Powder River County; John Jeakins, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 29-30)
  - Powder River County, 1967-1970 (Box 45, Folder 31-34)
  - Powell County, F. E. Ostrander, 1917 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Prairie County; G. E. Lewis, 1919-1924 (Box 45, Folder 36-41)
  - Prairie County; G. E. Lewis, C.A., 1925-1934 (Box 46, Folder 1-10)
  - Prairie County; F. A. Finch, C.A., 1935-1945 (Box 46, Folder 11-21)
  - Prairie County; Philip Wilson, C.A., 1946-1955 (Box 46, Folder 22-31)
  - Prairie County; Philip R. Wilson, Richard J. Reynolds, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Prairie County; P. R. Wilson, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Prairie County; Philip R. Wilson, C.A., 1958 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Prairie County; Philip R. Wilson, C.A., 1959 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Prairie County; Philip R. Wilson, 1960-1965 (Box 46, Folder 36-41)
  - Prairie County, 1967-1970 (Box 46, Folder 42-44)
  - Ravalli County; R. W. Fisher, 1917 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Ravalli County; L. H. Spring, 1918-1920 (Box 47, Folder 2-4)
  - Ravalli County; L. H. Spring, C. E. Carney, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Ravalli County; Chas. E. Carney, 1922 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Ravalli County; Chas. E. Carney, Louis A. Campbell, 1923 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Ravalli County; Louis A. Campbell, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Ravalli County; F. A. Givan, C.A., 1927-1929 (Box 47, Folder 9-11)
  - Ravalli County; C. H. Challey, Emergency Agent, 1933 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Report, Ravalli County; Charles Jarrett, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Ravalli County; S. N. Halvorson, C.A., 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 14-15)
  - Ravalli County; S. N. Halvorson, C.A.; H. K. Botch, Assistant Agent, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Ravalli County; Geo. R. McConnell, C.A.; H. K. Botch, Assit. C.A., 1947 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Ravalli County; Geo. E. McConnell, 1948-1949 (Box 47, Folder 18-19)
  - Ravalli County; Geo. McConnell, Leland Cade, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Ravalli County; W. P. Thomas, Alice Hancock, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Ravalli County; W. P. Thomas, Alice B. Hancock, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Ravalli County; Wm. P. Thomas, Alice Hancock, Earl Peace, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Ravalli County; Wm. P. Thomas, Gladys Musgrove, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Ravalli County; W. P. Thomas, Herbert H. Townsend, Gladys M. Musgrove, Earl J. Peace, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Ravalli County; William p. Thomas, Gladys M. Musgrove, Herbert H. Townsend, Donna M. Qualey, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Ravalli County; W. P. Thomas, Robert Ruthemeyer, Gladys M. Musgrove, Effie Enneberg, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Ravalli County; Bill Thomas, C.A., 1958 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Ravalli County; Bill Thomas, Agent; Sid Tietema, At Large; Bob Ruthemeyer, At Large; B. Hansen, Assoc.; Gladys Musgrove, H.D.A., 1959 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Ravalli County; W. P. Thomas, Gladys M. Musgrove, Robert J. Hanson, Robert Ruthemeyer, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Ravalli County; Robert J. Hansen, W. P. Thomas, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Ravalli County; Robert J. Hansen, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Ravalli County; James O. DeBree, 1963-1965 (Box 47, Folder 33-35)
  - Ravalli County; James DeBree, David Dickens, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Ravalli County, 1967-1970 (Box 47, Folder 37-40)
  - Richland County; A. D. Anderson, 1917-1919 (Box 47, Folder 41-43)
  - Richland County; Gladys Kyte, H.D.A., 1919 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Richland County; Harold F. DePue, 1920 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Richland County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1920 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - Richland County; Harold F. DePue, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - Richland County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1921 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - Richland County; Harold F. DePue, 1922 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - Richland County; Jessie Marion, H.D.A., 1922 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - Richland County; Harold F. DePue, 1923 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - Richland County; Jessie Marion, H.D.A., 1923 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - Richland County; Harold F. DePue, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - Richland County; Jessie Marion, H.D.A., 1924 (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - Richland County; H. F. DePue, C.A., 1925 (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - Richland County; Jessie Marion, H.D.A., 1925 (Box 47, Folder 56)
  - Richland County; H. F. DePue, C.A., 1926 (Box 47, Folder 57)
  - Richland County; Fannie Gorton, H.D.A., 1926 (Box 47, Folder 58)
  - Richland County; H. F. DePue, C.A., 1927 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Richland County; Fannie Gorton, H.D.A., 1927 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Richland County; H. F. DePue, C.A., 1928 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Richland County; Fannie Gorton, H.D.A., 1928 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Richland County; H. F. DePue, C.A., 1929 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Richland County; Fannie Gorton, H.D.A., 1929 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Richland County; H. F. DePue, C.A., 1930 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Richland County; Clara Dugan, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Richland County; Theodore Fosse, C.A., 1931 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Richland County; Clara Dugan, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Richland County; Theodore Fosse, C.A., 1932 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Richland County; Clara Dugan, H.D.A., 1932 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Richland County; Theo. Fosse, C.A., 1933 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Richland County; Theodore Fosse, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Richland County; Theodore Fosse, C.A., 1935 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Richland County; Theodore Fosse, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Richland County; Earl Bjork, Theodore Fosse, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Richland County; Theodore Fosse, 1938 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Richland County; Theodore Fosse, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Richland County; Earl W. Bjork, C.A., 1940 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Richland County; Earl W. Bjork, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Richland County; Marjorie Downs, H.D.A., 1941 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Richland County; E. W. Bjork, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Richland County; Marjorie Downs, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Richland County; Earl W. Bjork, Norbert Majerus, C.A., 1943 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Richland County; Marjorie E. Downs, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Richland County; Norbert Majerus, C.A., 1944 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Richland County; Marjorie Downs, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Richland County; Norbert Majerus, W. E. Corkins, C.A., 1945 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Richland County; Marjorie Downs, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Richland County; W. E. Corkins, C.A., 1946 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Richland County; Marjorie Downs, Leola Myra, H.D.A.s, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Richland County; W. E. Corkins, C.A., 1947 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Richland County; Leola Myra, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 48, Folder 34)